So we are coming to the end of the year of the snake, which is a year of shedding.
And I know so many people who this year feel like they have evolved all at once into a new space, a new person.
I do also, though, want to remind you that that person was always in you.
They were always there. You may not have given them credit because enough people around you wasn't giving them credit.
You may not have given that you credit because you didn't even realize how awesome it was that you was that you.
No, you may not have given them credit because you was really fighting for your life.
OK. So I want you to look at this email that some dude, a Mecca, had sent me in 2009.
And it came to my mind because I had to go into my emails for something and being an email hoarder, it actually came up.
But I read this and was like, wow, that man said opportunism, celebrity stalking and name.
Dropping. So being a hard worker, having friends who are famous and referring to your friends that are famous.
They mad when you are something that they are not and they can't make it make sense.
So then they do that.
I remember reading that and it hurting my feelings so crazy because it was such a wildly distorted version of who I was.
But then look at my response.
Ivy.
I was so shocked when I saw that response because it was so mature and generous.
She was in there the whole time.
But she was having to fight and mask her way through people like that.
And now she's living in her full vibrance, awakened, grounded and connected to something that is so much greater.
Collective liberation, soul and the earth.
So we're going to continue to keep getting more connected.
We're going to continue shedding those who cannot see us, who cannot feel us and who do not align with us.
And we're going to continue to remember that resistance is never futile, even if it just annoys them mofos.
Happy New Year.
Oh, and forget what he said.
Go on and big up yourself.